# **Zack Hersh**

zackshersh@gmail.com | 919-360-1962 | https://zackshersh.github.io/

# **About**

Full-stack web developer and designer who combines effective and informed design with engaging digital art. 4 years of experience in web development and drawing from 7 years of experience in art and design. Bachelor of Arts from the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Hussman School of Media and Journalism.

### Education

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Hussman School of Media & Journalism | 08/2019 - 12/2023

3.60 Overall GPA - 3.73 Major GPA

5 Semesters on Dean's List (UNC Suspended Dean's list in Spring and Fall 2020)

Web Development Bootcamp

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill | 01/2021 - 07/2021

- · Certificate of Completion Received
- Final project deemed most superior by instructors

# **Experience**

#### Guidehouse | Washington, DC

UX Intern | 06/2023 - 08/2023

- Implemented a system to track and integrate direct feedback from head administrator of government agency as part of an ongoing project to create a hotline for recipients of federal COVID-19 business loans
- Executed and presented a bid proposal for a mock federal contract which was selected by Guidehouse senior leadership over all other intern proposals
- Engaged in week-long mentorships with 10 consultants to learn about their areas of expertise within the realms of UX
  research, design and development and completed and received feedback on a mini-project in each area

#### UNC Blue Sky Innovations Lab at the Kenan Flagler Business School | Chapel Hill, NC

Innovation Fellow | 01/2023 - 12/2023

- Offered a specially created position based on proficiency demonstrated in Chief Innovation Officer's interactive media course at UNC.
- Developed and refined the user experience of a immersive Diversity, Equity and Inclusion VR training for a Fortune 100 Company.
- Initiated the development of techniques and custom tooling to enable team to more efficiently operate within a novel workflow
- Carried out multiple rounds of user testing to identify and resolve issues with products for the web and virtual reality

#### Freelance Web Developer and Graphic Designer

06/2022 - Present

- Created bespoke websites for clients such as an established multi-clinician psychotherapy practice and a lab within the UNC School of Medicine.
- Utilized UX and accessibility best practices, and tools such as React and Wordpress
- Completed graphic and motion design projects for a different lab within the UNC School of Medicine.

# **Relevant Projects**

#### **Expressive Metrics**

Fullstack Web Application | 06/2024 - 08/2024

- Personal project built with React, D3.js, Node.js, and MongoDB
- A website that presents a novel method for engaging with and exploring art by asking users to assign a numerical rating to subjective qualities of different artworks
- · Iterated through rounds of user testing in order to refine comprehension and ease of use
- Built a polished design system, based on user feedback, that centers on intuitive and tactile interaction

# **Skills**

#### Web Development

HTML/CSS, React, Node, MySQL & MongoDB, UI/UX design, UX Testing and Research, Three.js, D3.js, TailwindCSS, Figma/AdobeXD prototyping, Wordpress

## Traditional Digital Art & Design

Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, Premiere Pro), Blender3D